In addition, we need to know that sometimes there will be a fold on our clothes.
I don't know if you have such a question.
A lot of structures appeared all of a sudden.
That structure is just because I cut it and made the internal line habitually.
Just make it faster.
These pockets here are the same.
How do you do it on your pants?
How do you do it here?
I just skipped it.
Sometimes when you are making sleeves,
I don't know if you have noticed something.
It's very strange.
Some sleeves look very big on the top,
but the connection of the sleeves is very flat and there is no fold.
In fact, sometimes it is not without fold.
It will make a fold and shrink the excess.
Like me, we can draw two internal lines first.
Then fold it.
Fold it with the fold tool.
After folding it,
here, we align it to the outer line of the pattern and add two points to it.
It's convenient for us to fold it later.
Then sew it down with the line sewing tool.
Here we use the free sewing tool.
I'm wrong. It's not a free sewing tool.
The free sewing tool can determine the length of the fold and the length of the seam.
After sewing here,
this point here and the amount here will be shrunk.
After being shrunk, the length difference will be reduced.
Do you understand?
This is why some of the sleeves,
if you look from the back or from the concept picture,
the width difference of the sleeves is very large.
But when it comes to the sleeves,
when it comes to the sleeves,
it's gone.
That is, its fold disappears.
In fact, sometimes it will make some folds here.
To put this amount in.
Because it's folded.
In the fold position.
Including when we make shirts.
In fact, many shirts will add such folds.
Then it's the sleeves.
There are several ways to deal with the sleeves.
The first one is what we just used.
It's a flat sheet that's sewn directly.
In addition, sometimes it will be buttoned.
If it's buttoned,
we just cut its sewing line.
After that,
use the outside of the sheet to expand it and cut it out.
Because the outside of the sheet is expanded.
The part that expands is not folded.
There is no sewing line.
If there is no sewing line,
we just use the button to remember it.
This is a kind of sleeve.
There is another one.
It's the one on our last reference picture.
It's the sleeve of a pleated shirt.
Let's go back to before.
First of all, the sleeve of a pleated shirt.
It has a basic logic.
What is the sleeve of a pleated shirt?
Just like this.
This kind of sleeve.
It's like there's a rubber band inside.
First of all, it has a structure like this.
It has an inner layer.
It's a narrow sleeve.
And this narrow sleeve is not easy to stretch and deform.
Then there is a wide sleeve on the outer layer.
Wide, narrow, sewed together.
After sewing together,
let's take a look at the sewing line again.
The sewing line is a section.
It's not a whole circle.
It's a section.
The long side is sewed on the short side.
Then the long side is sewed on the short side.
This way, a whole long piece of fabric is wrapped outside the short fabric.
Sewed outside the short fabric.
That's how it's folded like this.
Do you understand?
OK.
It's stuck.
I forgot what I was talking about.
Forget it.
So the inner layer of the fabric is not easy to stretch.
Because the seam line of our fabric.
The seam line between the lines.
It itself will.
Divide the length.
That is to say.
In itself.
The short line will be stretched by the long line.
The long line will be shrunk by the short line.
So now if we want this kind of fold to become obvious.
We must make the long side follow the short side.
So the short side is not easy to stretch.
If it is not easy to stretch.
Is it the long side?
Must shrink.
It's as tight as the narrow side.
Just as short.
In this way.
The fold will be more obvious.
Do you understand?
So we need to give the inner layer of this fabric.
Use one.
You see.
You see it is flat.
And there is no stretch deformation.
This edge is very sharp.
Very straight.
It's because it's not easy to stretch.
Do you understand?
And we are doing this.
When it comes to this sleeve fabric.
Sometimes.
Sometimes we use the
Cologne layer to make the pattern.
Right?
The Cologne layer.
You can do two layers directly.
And because the Cologne layer comes out.
The pattern.
It will be sewn by itself.
It's the outer or inner of the original pattern.
But the Cologne layer has a problem.
Right?
The last version is so wide.
If we sew a whole circle.
A whole circle.
Is that the length difference.
Will be divided into a whole circle.
If it is divided into a whole circle.
It's not just a tree-shaped fold.
It includes this short side.
There will also be some folds.
It will be judged as a whole circle.
So what are we going to do?
We will modify the sewing line.
Can you understand?
So after the Cologne layer comes out.
You use the Cologne layer.
As a quick arrangement tool.
To use.
The sewing line it creates.
We are going to modify it.
And this kind of folding position.
Is going to change its sewing line type.
Into a turn.
And then.
Sorry.
The side is sewn together.
And then.
Then.
The top part.
Hilichel B&G.
It's made of P quase and Crystal clear.
Okay.
Then we.
hythm izquierd.
Okay.
It's already.
It's ought to be put on.
All right.
Oh, cut it.
Then proofing.
All right.
Then cut out this piece and then make it a down here.
Yes, here's the end.
That's it.
Let's use different là.
As for this,
I can see that this is forming.
This one is okay.
This one.
This is our live broadcast, every time I am preparing a lot of content, so everyone should be more serious when you listen to it, and follow our live broadcast more, because I really have a lot of things prepared in it.
Everyone, when you are watching, it's best to watch our live broadcast, don't watch the live broadcast, of course, I'm not saying that the friends in front of the screen don't watch the live broadcast, that is, they can't learn, that is, when you are live broadcasting, you can ask questions directly, if you are live broadcasting, you have to wait for a reply.
This time I have a lot of coughs, oh, don't tell me, I'm going to lie down with a few of them now.
I can't stand it anymore, wait a minute, I'll go and drink a few Tangzhangs, it's inconvenient for everyone to learn if you eat it, drink it well, drink a few Tangzhangs, and then you need to know the curse here outside of us.
First of all, the particle diameter of an outer version should be low, and if the particle diameter is not low enough, it is your grid.
Although the grid is much smoother, but there is a grid.
This is the case.
If the grid is too large, if the grid is too large, there is no way to form a very thin fold, which everyone can understand.
And the longer this length is, the more fabric there is, the thinner the fold.
Oh, no, I'm sure I'm going to finish it today.
And actually, I'm fine now.
This is me.
I've been sick.
It's just that after a while, the cough will be more serious.
In addition, we have finished this basic structure, and then our clothes have been cloned.
Oh, this is the fabric of the clothes.
These pockets are these.
There is a basic logic when there is a cloned layer.
That is, if your cloned clothes have a structure on the outside, you just put it in the cloned inside.
ah
Is it obvious that you don't change the fabric when you adjust the cuffs?
It depends on what you mean by simply adjusting the cuffs.
Because if you make a whole piece of clothing, it's just because of the simple adjustment of the cuffs.
I'll explain it to you this way.
If you only adjust the cuffs, the grid of the fabric will be cloned along with your cuffs adjustment.
Including you.
When you use the rules.
These tools.
It will actually affect the grid.
Then if you are a whole piece of clothing.
You are all the same proportion to shrink the cuffs.
That doesn't matter.
And if you only have one layer on this version.
In fact, it is equivalent to the width of your version.
Do you understand?
But when it comes to the seam line position, it's different.
Your seam line position.
For example, you give it some settings.
For example, you set the elasticity of these.
It will affect it.
So you adjust the cuffs.
Our usual habit is not to adjust the cuffs directly.
Instead, we will make a double-layer structure.
After I made a double-layer structure here.
We will apply a gold-like and silver-like shrink to the outer panels.
So that there is a gap between the panels inside and outside.
There is a gap.
This wrinkle will be obvious.
And it will be limited to this range.
And we have so many.
There will be some seam lines between the internal lines.
Look at me.
I used this.
It's the gold-like shrink of the outer panels.
After the shrinkage is increased.
This is because the inner panel is flat.
And then the outer panel.
The fabric becomes bigger.
The seam is on top.
Such a position.
There will be some natural wrinkles here.
Just like the traces of people wearing clothes.
You can see that our inner panel is relatively flat.
And it includes the physical properties of the fabric we use.
The inner layer.
The inner layer of the base layer.
It may be used for the fabric that is not easy to stretch.
And then the outer layer.
It will give it some.
For example, it's like the polyester fabric of the windbreaker.
Like this.
Yes.
Make one more layer.
No.
Making one more layer.
Sometimes it's not just for the small wrinkles.
Sometimes.
For example, we.
There was a live broadcast last year.
When talking about multi-layered clothing.
It's just some clothes.
It's different inside and outside.
You can't do the first layer.
The first layer is.
If you do the first layer.
The small wrinkles.
It's not that easy to come out.
And you do this double layer.
When it's a double-layer structure.
Well.
That is to say.
Your inner layer.
It looks from the inside.
You can also adjust it.
It includes your inner layer.
Sometimes you have to do these effects.
And your outer layer.
He doesn't have that.
That is.
You can't see the outer layer.
The pattern.
These are all for you to do double layers.
If you do a wide layer.
It's not that easy to come out.
That is.
These are the wrinkles that occur through the fine-tuning.
Do you understand?
Because you have a foundation.
That is.
Now you have these.
Isn't there a seam line?
These things.
These things will limit you.
This big board.
It can only be in this area of ​​the small board.
But if you don't have this small board.
To limit.
Then you have a whole dress.
It's just a big dress.
Put it on the model.
It's not a big dress.
It's sewn on a small board.
It's a little bit smaller.
On the board.
And then there's some.
Pulling fabric.
There's some fine fabric.
These.
It's a different concept.
That is.
If you only use one layer.
Use shrink.
Just enlarge the board.
And what we're doing now.
Is to sew the big board.
On top of the small board.
Let it have wrinkles.
So.
Simply put.
You can't do a layer.
All right.
Other than that.
We have some other ways.
You can add wrinkles.
That's it.
This is an example of a foldable board.
You can add wrinkles.
Use.
Use armhole.
Right.
The correct number.
Give it some wrinkles to add.
Because you see.
Uh.
Sometimes we use these tighter.
Well.
It should not product in the store.
Because.
Because this file is made.
More.
A file with higher completeness.
You can see.
In the past, I uploaded clothes that were very troublesome for me, such as motorcycle clothes, and I uploaded them all to the store.
I saw that the download rate was very low, and you guys didn't even download it for me.
And you know, when you upload it to the background, you have to deal with documents, and it's more troublesome.
Let's look at your like support rate, okay?
It's not the dollar, I uploaded it to the store for free.
When did I upload documents for money?
Which document of mine is not for you to upload for free?
I made a rendering for you again, and then I color it for you again, and then I did all those things for you.
Then no one downloaded it for me.
Okay.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
I can't stand it anymore.
The motorcycle I used to ride, including this glove, are all free.
I used to make them for you.
Upload it to the website, and no one will download it.
And then, like us, the chief of staff, I went to study the bottom of the military uniform.
I saw a lot of military uniforms.
There are actually some little things on the bottom.
It's just a little bulge or a little wrinkle.
So when we're doing this file, sometimes it's connected.
It's to mammothdesigner3w.mammothdesigner.com.
And then there's a store after you go up there.
There are a lot of free ones after you enter the store.
Including this one.
This is very handsome.
This virtual model.
Oh, I can't take off this sunglasses.
This includes our virtual models.
These are the ones that have a lot of hearts.
Including the shoes.
There are a lot of things.
There are a lot of free things.
You can go up and have a look.
Okay.
Pull it back and talk about it.
Here I used the right-hand ruler to smear along the seam line.
Okay.
Ah.
Oh.
No.
So.
qualified
I don't understand, some things are uploaded by the cloud team, but it doesn't mean that only the cloud can use this thing, so the direction you understand is the wrong one.
All files are used secretly, and then if you think that the position of the smear plus the position of the ruler is added too much, then we can use the negative ruler to recover it.
Then, because of the positive shrink rate, especially my habit is to give it a smear with this kind of inner line to increase some wrinkles.
Including the bottom here, you added some positive rules to it, because there is a lot of material added,
the whole wrinkle will be reduced.
The effect of the wrinkle will come out.
For example, it's better to add a little bit.
There will always be some random effects.
Is it only the MD clothing project that makes it a little more troublesome to automatically wear it?
First of all, automatically wear it, its English is retarget draping.
In fact, it is to change the model to wear it.
There is no model in the project, then how do you automatically wear it?
You have to wear it on your shoes.
Are you going to do it automatically?
If it's automatic, I think it's not very convenient to do it automatically now.